<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
    xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
    xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
    xmlns:admin="http://webns.net/mvcb/"
    xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
    xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">

    <channel>
    
    <title>Cognition Caps</title>
    <link>http://wearcognition.com/index.php/blog</link>
    <description>Cognition Caps Blog</description>
    <dc:rights>Copyright 2012</dc:rights>
    <dc:date>2012-07-18T03:20:47-06:00</dc:date>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our blog feed has moved!</title>
      <link>http://wearcognition.com/blog</link>
      <guid>http://wearcognition.com/blog#When:12:07:47Z</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hi, everyone! We're very excited to launch our new site. As a result, our RSS feeds have been updated and moved. This feed will no longer be active;
              please unfollow it and subscribe to the new one here: <a href="http://wearcognition.com/feeds/blog-atom.xml</a>.</p>

          <p>Thanks!</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:date>2012-07-18T03:20:47-06:00</dc:date>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>2012 Sadie Hawkins Day Style Ride</title>
      <link>http://wearcognition.com/index.php/blog/2012-sadie-hawkins-day-style-ride/</link>
      <guid>http://wearcognition.com/index.php/blog/2012-sadie-hawkins-day-style-ride/#When:04:04:32Z</guid>
      <description>We're happy to once again sponsor this year's Sadie Hawkins Day Style Ride! What is it, you ask?</description>
      <dc:date>2012-08-20T04:04:32Z</dc:date>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>We&#8217;re back!</title>
      <link>http://wearcognition.com/index.php/blog/were-back1/</link>
      <guid>http://wearcognition.com/index.php/blog/were-back1/#When:02:20:47Z</guid>
      <description>You feel a tingle on the back of your neck. Static crackles on the TV&#8230;and it&#8217;s not just cosmic microwave background radiation. What was that noise?! Something strange is going on here&#8230;

That&#8217;s right, ordering has been reenabled on the site! We&#8217;ve given the capmaking gnomes a stern talking to, reduced their mythical sauce rations, and told them to get back to work. Thanks for your patience while we were on hiatus!

And as always, there are some cool new improvements in the works&#8230;</description>
      <dc:date>2012-06-26T02:20:47-06:00</dc:date>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>The LepreCog</title>
      <link>http://wearcognition.com/index.php/blog/the-leprecog/</link>
      <guid>http://wearcognition.com/index.php/blog/the-leprecog/#When:13:13:43Z</guid>
      <description>A St. Patrick&#8217;s Day Alley Cat in Madison , WI

Here&#8217;s a local event coming up here in Madison!
Details:

BB Clarke Beach
1pm Registration
2pm Start

Bring your bike, bag and 5$
Irish Attire encouraged

Check out the tumblr site for more photos and details.</description>
      <dc:date>2012-03-13T13:13:43-06:00</dc:date>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Broken Hearts and Bicycle Parts 8</title>
      <link>http://wearcognition.com/index.php/blog/broken-hearts-and-bicycle-parts-8/</link>
      <guid>http://wearcognition.com/index.php/blog/broken-hearts-and-bicycle-parts-8/#When:13:06:56Z</guid>
      <description>One of the awesome events we sponsor yearly is the Broken Hearts and Bicycle Parts series put on by the Sopo Bicycle Co&#45;op in Atlanta. Well, the 8th edition coming up shortly! Pre&#45;registration is open, check it out!</description>
      <dc:date>2012-03-13T13:06:56-06:00</dc:date>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>We&#8217;re back!</title>
      <link>http://wearcognition.com/index.php/blog/were-back/</link>
      <guid>http://wearcognition.com/index.php/blog/were-back/#When:21:08:23Z</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone! Unfortunately, the day after we left the country and went off the grid two weeks ago our web hosting account experienced a bit of a hiccup and the site was down. What timing! Sorry for any inconvenience that might have caused, but we&#8217;ve got it sorted out and we&#8217;re open for business once again.

Thanks for your patience!</description>
      <dc:date>2012-02-05T21:08:23-06:00</dc:date>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Shipments on hold</title>
      <link>http://wearcognition.com/index.php/blog/shipments-delayed/</link>
      <guid>http://wearcognition.com/index.php/blog/shipments-delayed/#When:15:00:50Z</guid>
      <description>Hi all! The entire Cognition staff (i.e., both of us) will be out of the country and off the grid for a couple of weeks, starting tonight. Please note that no orders will be shipped out until we return, and it&#8217;s unlikely we&#8217;ll be able to respond to emails.

See you when we get back!</description>
      <dc:date>2012-01-22T15:00:50-06:00</dc:date>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Sadie Hawkins Style Ride</title>
      <link>http://wearcognition.com/index.php/blog/sadie-hawkins-style-ride/</link>
      <guid>http://wearcognition.com/index.php/blog/sadie-hawkins-style-ride/#When:14:56:28Z</guid>
      <description>Coming up soon (November 5th) in Chicago is the 6th annual Sadie Hawkin&#8217;s Style Ride! Kelly and I (and quite a few other Madison folks, if I recall correctly) have done this event once or twice, and it&#8217;s been a blast. We&#8217;ve also been excited to sponsor it over the years, so check it out! http://sadiehawkinschicago.com/

From the site:
So what&#8217;s a &#8216;Sadie&#8217; you say?
The Sadie&#8217;s is geared to be a fun ride for all cyclists. This is a great first ride if you don&#8217;t have experience but also challenging enough for the seasoned rider. Sadie&#8217;s is specifically geared to encourage women to come out and ride in a friendly and non&#45;intimidating event. And guess what? It&#8217;s a charity event! So no matter what, you&#8217;re helping out The Chicago Women&#8217;s Health Center&#8217;s efforts to keep women healthy, educated about their bodies and out riding their bikes!</description>
      <dc:date>2011-10-06T14:56:28-06:00</dc:date>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Cirque du SoGay</title>
      <link>http://wearcognition.com/index.php/blog/cirque-du-sogay1/</link>
      <guid>http://wearcognition.com/index.php/blog/cirque-du-sogay1/#When:00:27:08Z</guid>
      <description>Coming up right around the corner in Minneapolis is third edition of the fabulous Cirque du SoGay. From their site:
Cirque du SoGAY is Queer Bike Gang (QBG)&#8216;s annual bicycle tour of the hottest Queer establishments in the Twin Cities.&amp;nbsp; Cirque du SoGay was created to celebrate Queer culture while connecting people to LGBTQ resources in the community, and is followed by an awards ceremony, performances, and a big gay dance party.
We supported the event with some caps last year and have again revived the special edition Rainbow Cap in honor of the event.

Sounds like a totally awesome time, if you&#8217;re in or around the Minneapolis area, make sure to check it out! Pre&#45;registration is open September 30 at 5:00pm, or register in person.</description>
      <dc:date>2011-09-29T00:27:08-06:00</dc:date>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Dayton Pedal Party</title>
      <link>http://wearcognition.com/index.php/blog/dayton-pedal-party/</link>
      <guid>http://wearcognition.com/index.php/blog/dayton-pedal-party/#When:13:19:28Z</guid>
      <description>Neal in Dayton is organizing a two&#45;day ride from Dayton to Cincinnati and back, on Sept. 24 and 25. Nothing like breathing the cool fall air and a couple of days in the saddle with some pals!

Check out daytonpedalparty.tumblr.com/ for more info.</description>
      <dc:date>2011-09-06T13:19:28-06:00</dc:date>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>The Bicycle Cap: A Love Story</title>
      <link>http://wearcognition.com/index.php/blog/the-bicycle-cap-a-love-story/</link>
      <guid>http://wearcognition.com/index.php/blog/the-bicycle-cap-a-love-story/#When:19:12:12Z</guid>
      <description>Our interest in this story is twofold: first, it&#8217;s a great story of cap related, pedal powered bicycle love. Secondly, I believe that Charly, the guy who builds the bike&#45;powered sewing setup, is wearing a Cognition cap in some of the shots!
The Bicycle Cap by peSeta for the New Museum from casa peSeta on Vimeo.

Cameo!


Big thanks to Chris for forwarding this to us.</description>
      <dc:date>2011-06-28T19:12:12-06:00</dc:date>
    </item>

    
    </channel>
</rss>
